<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank Johns</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Frank Johns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Frank Johns LP Consulting</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Affiliations</title>
      <link>/affiliations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/affiliations/</guid>
      <description> Chairman and Founding Member of the Loss Prevention Foundation Member of the Loss Prevention Magazine Editorial Board Member of the RILA Loss Prevention Steering Committee for over ten years, including two years as Chair Former Board Member of The Office Depot Foundation                </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting Services</title>
      <link>/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/consulting/</guid>
      <description>Our consulting services are built upon the model of developing a store-centric loss prevention department for your company. We will meet with you at your location to evaluate your companies needs and determine a solution for you. We will assist you in building a loss prevention team from the ground up or redirecting your current team to deliver a quality service program.
Listed below are some areas in which we can help your company:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Our loss prevention philosophy is basic: a store-centric loss prevention program builds a business culture of reducing shrink. Our program’s strategy focuses on delivering quality service to all business partners within your brand including store operations, merchandising, supply chain, human resources, finance, etc. This strategy replaces the traditional focus of loss prevention, which is solely to lower shrink through apprehension methods.
Our consulting services can show you how to transform your team into a well-rounded business partner that understands more than apprehending shoplifters and/or investigating internal theft cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profile</title>
      <link>/profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/profile/</guid>
      <description>Frank Johns has over 35 years of experience in the retail industry, which includes a dynamic blend of loss prevention and store operations executive management. This experience has influenced his philosophy of developing a store-centric approach to loss prevention. Frank’s career consists of many strategic positions:
 Senior Vice President of Stores, Loss Prevention, Audit, Ethics and Compliance with A.C. Moore, a regional craft retailer Vice President of Global Loss Prevention for Office Depot Director of Loss Prevention and Internal Audit for Mervyn’s Department stores Various positions at Montgomery Ward including District Manager for stores in Los Angeles, National Retail Marketing Manager for Furniture, Store Manager, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>A.C. Moore Arts &amp;amp; Crafts Inc.  Senior V.P. of Stores, Loss Prevention, Audit, Ethics and Compliance
August 2008 to June 2010
 Responsible for profit and loss including operating income, store controllable expenses and pretax profit in 133 retail locations. Responsibilities also include management of the loss prevention organization including shrink control, fraud, theft, workers compensation and general liability. Also responsible for strategic development and execution of audit program including SOX compliance and general management of corporate ethics and compliance policy, reporting to the Chairman of the Audit Committee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>